

www.katechang.info +1 (714) 392-6153 katehbchang@gmail.com

An adept collaborative UI/UX designer, blending past design & production experience in product development, excels at simplifying intricate concepts and achieving a user-friendly experience through exceptional organization and prioritizing skills.

EDUCATION

University of California, Irvine (UCI)

Irvine, California | Sept - Dec 2008

Undergraduate studies

Beijing Foreign Studies Univ.

Beijing, China | JAN 2012

Bachelor's in Business Chinese

- Graduated with Highest Honors
- Received National Scholarship

CERTIFICATE

- Figma UI/UX Design Essentials [Udemy]
- Design Rules: Principles + Practices for Great UI Design [Udemy]
- UX Strategy Fundamentals [Udemy]
- Figma HTML CSS JavaScript in Web Design and UI UX Design [Udemy]

TOOLS

- Figma, Adobe XD, Zeplin
- Adobe Photoshop & Illustrator
- HTML, JavaScript, CSS
- Microsoft Suites

LANGUAGES

- Korean
- English
- Mandarin Chinese

EXPERIENCE

UI/UX Designer | Torrid

City of Industry, CA | June 2022 - Present

- Collaborate closely with cross-functional teams including UX designers, product managers, and developers to create visually stunning and intuitive user interfaces.
- Design responsive web and mobile interfaces that prioritize usability and accessibility while maintaining aesthetic appeal.
- Develop and maintain a consistent visual language and design system that aligns with brand guidelines and enhances user engagement.

Freelance Product (UI/UX) Designer | WG

Anaheim, CA | February 2024 - Present

- Solo product designer focused on building a user-friendly web platform out from scratch
- Engineered an inclusive and accessive design to accommodate not only the target users but also potential audiences.
- Worked closely with software developer to address critical business and usability issues upfront.

Senior Production Designer | Torrid

City of Industry, CA | November 2015 - May 2022

- Partnered with teams of designers, product developers, and art directors to create quality print designs that bring to life the company's visual identity across all touchpoints.
- Supervised junior artists to become integral parts of the creative team with refined, efficient processes and compelling art concepts.
- Elevated brand image by developing on-trend art that differentiated the company from competitors and generated increase in sales that led to double bonus in the year end.